<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Madhva Vahini</string>
    <string name="splash_description">Developed by Aishwarya Software, Bengaluru</string>
    <string name="app_version">v %s</string>
    <!--Errors-->
    <string name="empty_categories">No categories found for query %s</string>
    <string name="empty_subcategories">No sub-categories found for query %s</string>
    <string name="empty_sub_to_sub_categories">No sub-to-sub-categories found for query %s</string>
    <string name="empty_files">No files found for query %s</string>
    <string name="check_internet">Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="server_error">Some server error occurred</string>

    <!--Search-->
    <plurals name="numberOfSearchResults">
        <item quantity="one">%d result found.</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d results found.</item>
    </plurals>

    <!--Authentication-->
    <string name="login">Sign In</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="has_account">Already have an account ? </string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\'t have an account yet ? </string>
    <string name="register">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="name_header">Name</string>
    <string name="name_hint">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="phone_header">Mobile number</string>
    <string name="phone_hint">Enter your mobile number</string>
    <string name="password_header">Password</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Enter password</string>
    <string name="login_success">Logged in successfully.</string>
    <string name="signin_success">Signed in successfully.</string>

    <string name="get_otp">Get Otp</string>
    <string name="verify_otp">Verify Otp</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password</string>

    <!--Menu-->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome %s,</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="about">About us</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <!--Category-->
    <string name="category">Categories</string>
    <string name="category_search">Search for any category</string>

    <!--Sub Category-->
    <string name="sub_cat">Sub Categories</string>
    <string name="sub_cat_search">Search for any sub-category</string>

    <!--Sub to sub Category-->
    <string name="sub_to_sub_cat">Sub to sub categories</string>
    <string name="sub_to_sub_cat_search">Search for any category or files</string>

    <!--Files-->
    <string name="files">Files</string>
    <string name="files_search">Search for any file</string>
    <string name="document_search">Search for any word or line…</string>

    <!--Files details-->
    <string name="files_details">File Details</string>
    <!--Language-->
    <string name="en">English</string>
    <string name="sa">संस्कृत</string>
    <string name="kn">ಕನ್ನಡ</string>
    <string name="te">తెలుగు</string>
    <string name="ta">தமிழ்</string>

    <!--Contact-->
    <string name="sub_heading">In case of any difficulty or queries please contact us on the details below :</string>
    <string name="name">Aishwarya Software Solutions</string>
    <string name="email">info@aishwaryasoftware.in</string>
    <string name="phone">+91 6302362937</string>
    <string name="address">#7, Near Trinetralaya Eye Care, Dasarahalli South Block, Sri nagar, BSK 1st Stage, Bengaluru - 560050</string>

    <!--Support-->
    <string name="support_sub_heading">In case of any technical queries/complaints, please reach us at :</string>
    <string name="support_name">Aishwarya Software Solutions</string>
    <string name="support_email">cvamsik5@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="support_phone">+91 7337763918</string>
    <string name="support_location">Bengaluru</string>

    <!-- About us -->
    <string name="contact_mail">aishwaryasoftware22@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="about_us_header">ಮಧ್ವ ವಾಹಿನಿ</string>
    <string name="about_us">ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಸದ್ಭಕ್ತರಿಗೂ ಸ್ವಾಗತ !
ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಸದ್ಭಕ್ತರ ಪ್ರತಿ ನಿತ್ಯ  ಮಂತ್ರ ಸ್ತೋತ್ರ  ಸುಳಾದಿಗಳ ಹಾಡುಗಳ ಪಾರಾಯಣಕ್ಕಾಗಿ ನಿರ್ಮಾಣ ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ. ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಯಾವ ದೇವರ ಹಾಡುಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಸ್ತೋತ್ರಗಳು  ಬೇಕಾದರೂ ಸೆಲೆಕ್ಟ್ ಮಾಡಿಕೊಂಡು , ಆ ದೇವರ ಹಾಡುಗಳನ್ನು , ಸ್ತೋತ್ರಗಳನ್ನು ಓಪನ್ ಮಾಡಿಕೊಂಡು ಪಾರಾಯಣ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ನಲ್ಲಿ ಇರುವ ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಂಸ್ಕೃತ , ಕನ್ನಡ , ತೆಲುಗು , ಇಂಗ್ಲಿಷ್ ಮತ್ತು ತಮಿಳ ಭಾಷೆಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಲ್ಯಾಂಗ್ವೇಜ್ ಟ್ರಾನ್ಸ್ಲೇಟರ್ ಎಂಬ ಆಪ್ಷನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬಳಿಸಿಕೊಂಡು ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಇರುವ ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒಂದು ಬಾರಿ ಪೇಮೆಂಟ್ ಪೇಜ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ತೋರಿಸಿರುವ  ಹಣವನ್ನು ಪಾವತಿ ಮಾಡಿ ಬಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಇರುವ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಅಲ್ಲದೆ ಭವಿಷ್ಯತ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಹಾಕುವ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಕೂಡ ಉಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಉಪಯೋಗಿಸಬಹುದು. ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಸದ್ಭಕ್ತರು ಈ ಮಧ್ವ ವಾಹಿನಿ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ನ ಬಳಿಸಿ ದೈನಿಂದಿನ ಜೀವನದಲ್ಲಿ ಉಪಯೋಗ ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.
</string>

    <string name="terms_and_condition">Terms and condition</string>
    <string name="google_play">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="tnc">Thank you for accessing/shopping at Madhwa Vahini app (https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini). This mobile application  is owned by Aishwarya Software Solutions (hereinafter referred to as “https://aishwaryasoftware.in/”). By accessing, shopping on this app, you indicate your unconditional acceptance of these terms &amp; conditions. We reserve this right, in our sole discretion, to update or revise these terms &amp; conditions. Continued use of the app following the posting of any changes to the ‘terms &amp; conditions’, constitutes your acceptance of those changes. At “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini-”, we try our best to create a space where you can explore and shop for all your favorite things in a safe and secure environment. All products and information displayed on “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” constitutes an "invitation to offer". “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” reserves the right to accept or reject your offer. Your order for purchase, constitutes your "offer" which shall be subject to the terms and conditions as listed below.</string>
    <string name="tnc_header_1">1. Eligibility to use our app</string>
    <string name="tnc_header_2">2. Membership</string>
    <string name="tnc_header_3">3. Electronic Communications</string>
    <string name="tnc_header_4">4. Reviews, Feedback, Submissions</string>
    <string name="tnc_header_5">5. Accuracy of Content/ Information of Products on the Web app</string>

    <string name="tnc_body_1">Use of the app is available only to persons who can legally enter into contracts under applicable laws. Persons who are "incompetent to contract", within the meaning of the Indian Contract Act, 1872 including un-discharged insolvents etc. are not eligible to use the app. “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” reserves the right to terminate your access to the app if it discovers that you are under the age of 18 years or suffers from any other disability, as recognized under Indian Contract Act, 1872.</string>
    <string name="tnc_body_2">Although it\'s not essential to have an account to shop with “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini”, you can shop as a guest. As a member, you agree to provide true, accurate, current, and complete information about yourself as prompted by the app\'s registration form. Registration where prohibited under any law shall be void. “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” reserves the right to revoke or terminate your registration for any reason at any time, without notice.</string>
    <string name="tnc_body_3">When you use the app or send emails or other data, information or communicate to us, you agree and understand that you are communicating with us electronically and give your consent to receive communications electronically from us periodically, when required.</string>
    <string name="tnc_body_4">All reviews, comments, feedback, postcards, suggestions, ideas, and other submissions disclosed, submitted or offered to “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” directly or otherwise disclosed, submitted or offered in connection with your use of this app (collectively referred to "Comments") will remain “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” property. Such disclosure, submission or offer of any comments shall constitute an assignment to “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” of all worldwide rights, titles and interests in all copyrights and other intellectual properties in the comments,thus, it exclusively owns all such rights, titles and interests and shall not be limited in any way in its use, commercial or otherwise. “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” will be entitled to use, reproduce, disclose, modify, adapt, create derivative works from, publish, display and distribute any comments you submit for any purpose whatsoever, without restriction and without compensating you in any way. “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” is and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any Comments in confidence; or (2) to pay you any compensation for any Comments; or (3) to respond to any Comments. You agree that any comments submitted by you to the app will not violate this policy or any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right(s), and will not cause injury to any person or entity. You further agree that no comments submitted by you to the app will be libelous or otherwise unlawful, threatening, abusive or obscene material, or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings or any form of "spam".
“https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” does not regularly review posted comments, but does reserve the right (but not the obligation) to monitor and edit or remove any comment submitted to the app. You grant “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” the right to use the name that you submit in connection with any of the posted comments. You agree not to use a false email address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of any Comments you submit. You are and shall remain solely responsible for the content of any comments you make and you agree to indemnify “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” and its affiliates for all claims resulting from any Comments you submit, we take no responsibility and assume no liability for any comments submitted by you or any third party.
</string>
    <string name="tnc_body_5">While “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” strives to provide accurate product and pricing information, typographical errors may occur. In the event that a product is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information due to an error in pricing or product information, “https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.ass.madhwavahini” shall have the right, on our sole discretion, to modify the price of the products, or information of the products or to refuse or cancel any orders placed for that product, unless the product has already been dispatched. In the event.</string>

    <string name="tnc_changes">Changes to This Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tnc_changes_body">We may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are
advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of
any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.
These terms and conditions are effective as of 2023-12-11.</string>

    <string name="tnc_contact_us">If you have any questions or suggestions about our Terms and Conditions, do
not hesitate to contact us at </string>


    <!--////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////-->


    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_body">Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru built the Madhva Vahini app as a Free
app. This SERVICE is provided by Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru at
no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use,
and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of
information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is
used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your
information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms
and Conditions, which are accessible at Madhva Vahini unless otherwise defined
in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide
us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we
request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.
The app does use third-party services that may collect information used to
identify you.
Link to the privacy policy of third-party service providers used by the app
Google Play Services

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you
will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us.
Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy
policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not
knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years
of age. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with
personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a
parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with
personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do the
necessary actions.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to
review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes
by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
This policy is effective as of 2023-02-13
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not
hesitate to contact us at aishwaryasoftware22@gmail.com.</string>


    <string name="refund">Refund Policy</string>
    <string name="refund_policy_body">Since the Mobile Application offers non-tangible, irrevocable goods we do not
provide refunds after the product is purchased, which you acknowledge prior to
purchasing any product in the Mobile Application. Please make sure that you’ve
carefully read product description before making a purchase.
</string>
    <string name="refund_policy_contact">
    If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints regarding this refund policy,
we encourage you to contact us using the details below:
</string>
    <string name="shipping_policy">Shipping Policy</string>
    <string name="shipping_policy_body">Since the Mobile Application offers non-tangible, irrevocable goods we do not
provide any shipping facility after the product is purchased, which you
acknowledge prior to purchasing any product in the Mobile Application.
</string>
    <string name="shipping_policy_contact">
        If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints regarding this refund policy,
we encourage you to contact us using the details below:
    </string>


</resources>