<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Madhva Vahini</string>
    <string name="splash_description">Developed by Aishwarya Software, Bengaluru</string>
    <string name="app_version">v %s</string>
    <!--Errors-->
    <string name="empty_categories">No categories found for query %s</string>
    <string name="empty_subcategories">No sub-categories found for query %s</string>
    <string name="empty_sub_to_sub_categories">No sub-to-sub-categories found for query %s</string>
    <string name="empty_files">No files found for query %s</string>
    <string name="check_internet">Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="server_error">Some server error occurred</string>

    <!--Search-->
    <plurals name="numberOfSearchResults">
        <item quantity="one">%d result found.</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d results found.</item>
    </plurals>

    <!--Authentication-->
    <string name="login">Sign In</string>
    <string name="has_account">Already have an account ? </string>
    <string name="no_account">Don\'t have an account yet ? </string>
    <string name="register">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="name_header">Name</string>
    <string name="name_hint">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="phone_header">Mobile number</string>
    <string name="phone_hint">Enter your mobile number</string>
    <string name="password_header">Password</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Enter password</string>
    <string name="login_success">Logged in successfully.</string>
    <string name="signin_success">Signed in successfully.</string>

    <!--Menu-->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome %s,</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="about">About us</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="support">Support</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <!--Category-->
    <string name="category">Categories</string>
    <string name="category_search">Search for any category</string>

    <!--Sub Category-->
    <string name="sub_cat">Sub Categories</string>
    <string name="sub_cat_search">Search for any sub-category</string>

    <!--Sub to sub Category-->
    <string name="sub_to_sub_cat">Sub to sub categories</string>
    <string name="sub_to_sub_cat_search">Search for any category or files</string>

    <!--Files-->
    <string name="files">Files</string>
    <string name="files_search">Search for any file</string>

    <!--Files details-->
    <string name="files_details">File Details</string>

    <!--Contact-->
    <string name="sub_heading">In case of any difficulty or queries please contact us on the details below :</string>
    <string name="name">Aishwarya Software Solutions</string>
    <string name="email">info@aishwaryasoftware.in</string>
    <string name="phone">+91 6302362937</string>
    <string name="address">#7, Near Trinetralaya Eye Care, Dasarahalli South Block, Sri nagar, BSK 1st Stage, Bengaluru - 560050</string>

    <!--Support-->
    <string name="support_sub_heading">In case of any technical queries/complaints, please reach us at :</string>
    <string name="support_name">Aishwarya Software Solutions</string>
    <string name="support_email">cvamsik5@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="support_phone">+91 7337763918</string>
    <string name="support_location">Bengaluru</string>

    <!-- About us -->
    <string name="contact_mail">aishwaryasoftware22@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="about_us_header">ಮಧ್ವ ವಾಹಿನಿ</string>
    <string name="about_us">ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಸದ್ಭಕ್ತರಿಗೂ ಸ್ವಾಗತ ! ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಸದ್ಭಕ್ತರ ಪ್ರತಿ ನಿತ್ಯ  ಮಂತ್ರ ಸ್ತೋತ್ರ  ಸುಳಾದಿಗಳ ಹಾಡುಗಳ ಪಾರಾಯಣಕ್ಕಾಗಿ ನಿರ್ಮಾಣ ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ. ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಯಾವ ದೇವರ ಹಾಡುಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಸ್ತೋತ್ರಗಳು  ಬೇಕಾದರೂ ಸೆಲೆಕ್ಟ್ ಮಾಡಿಕೊಂಡು , ಆ ದೇವರ ಹಾಡುಗಳನ್ನು , ಸ್ತೋತ್ರಗಳನ್ನು ಓಪನ್ ಮಾಡಿಕೊಂಡು ಪಾರಾಯಣ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು. ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ನಲ್ಲಿ ಇರುವ ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಂಸ್ಕೃತ , ಕನ್ನಡ , ತೆಲುಗು , ಇಂಗ್ಲಿಷ್ ಮತ್ತು ತಮಿಳ ಭಾಷೆಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಲ್ಯಾಂಗ್ವೇಜ್ ಟ್ರಾನ್ಸ್ಲೇಟರ್ ಎಂಬ ಆಪ್ಷನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬಳಿಸಿಕೊಂಡು ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಈ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಇರುವ ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒಂದು ಬಾರಿ ಪೇಮೆಂಟ್ ಪೇಜ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ತೋರಿಸಿರುವ  ಹಣವನ್ನು ಪಾವತಿ ಮಾಡಿ ಬಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಇರುವ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಅಲ್ಲದೆ ಭವಿಷ್ಯತ್ ಅಲ್ಲಿ ಹಾಕುವ ಕಂಟೆಂಟ್ ಕೂಡ ಉಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಉಪಯೋಗಿಸಬಹುದು. ಎಲ್ಲಾ ಸದ್ಭಕ್ತರು ಈ ಮಧ್ವ ವಾಹಿನಿ ಅಪ್ಲಿಕೇಶನ್ ನ ಬಳಿಸಿ ದೈನಿಂದಿನ ಜೀವನದಲ್ಲಿ ಉಪಯೋಗ ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.</string>

    <string name="terms_and_condition">Terms and condition</string>
    <string name="google_play">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_body1">By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you –
you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the
app. You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or our
trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code
of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages or
make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trademarks, copyright,
database rights, and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to
Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru.
Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru is committed to ensuring that the app
is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to
make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any
reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it
very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
The Madhva Vahini app stores and processes personal data that you have
provided to us, to provide our Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone
and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak
or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and
limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make
your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your
phone’s security features and it could mean that the Madhva Vahini app won’t
work properly or at all.
The app does use third-party services that declare their Terms and Conditions.
Link to Terms and Conditions of third-party service providers used by the app</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions_body2">
        You should be aware that there are certain things that Aishwarya Software
Solutions , Bengaluru will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app
will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be
Wi-Fi or provided by your mobile network provider, but Aishwarya Software
Solutions , Bengaluru cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full
functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your
data allowance left.

If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that
the terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a
result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the
duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third-party charges.
In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including
roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e.
region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for
the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that
you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
Along the same lines, Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru cannot always
take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that
your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to
avail the Service, Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru cannot accept
responsibility.
With respect to Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru’s responsibility for
your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that
although we endeavor to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do
rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available
to you. Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru accepts no liability for any loss,
direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality
of the app.
At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on
Android – the requirements for the system(and for any additional systems we
decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to
download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Aishwarya Software
Solutions , Bengaluru does not promise that it will always update the app so that
it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed
on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the
application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and
may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you.
Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses
granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if
needed) delete it from your device.
    </string>

    <string name="tnc_changes">Changes to This Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tnc_changes_body">We may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are
advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of
any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.
These terms and conditions are effective as of 2023-02-13.</string>

    <string name="tnc_contact_us">If you have any questions or suggestions about our Terms and Conditions, do
not hesitate to contact us at </string>


    <!--////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////-->


    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_body">Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru built the Madhva Vahini app as a Free
app. This SERVICE is provided by Aishwarya Software Solutions , Bengaluru at
no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use,
and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of
information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is
used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your
information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms
and Conditions, which are accessible at Madhva Vahini unless otherwise defined
in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide
us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we
request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.
The app does use third-party services that may collect information used to
identify you.
Link to the privacy policy of third-party service providers used by the app
Google Play Services

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you
will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us.
Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy
policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not
knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years
of age. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with
personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a
parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with
personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do the
necessary actions.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to
review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes
by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
This policy is effective as of 2023-02-13
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not
hesitate to contact us at aishwaryasoftware22@gmail.com.</string>
    <string name="refund">Refund Policy</string>
    <string name="refund_policy_body">Since the Mobile Application offers non-tangible, irrevocable goods we do not
provide refunds after the product is purchased, which you acknowledge prior to
purchasing any product in the Mobile Application. Please make sure that you’ve
carefully read product description before making a purchase.
</string>
    <string name="refund_policy_contact">
    If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints regarding this refund policy,
we encourage you to contact us using the details below:
</string>
    <string name="shipping_policy">Shipping Policy</string>
    <string name="shipping_policy_body">Since the Mobile Application offers non-tangible, irrevocable goods we do not
provide any shipping facility after the product is purchased, which you
acknowledge prior to purchasing any product in the Mobile Application.
</string>
    <string name="shipping_policy_contact">
        If you have any questions, concerns, or complaints regarding this refund policy,
we encourage you to contact us using the details below:
    </string>

</resources>